[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 2, "question": "But at what cost?", "question_tokens": ["But", "at", "what", "cost", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 3, "answer": "It shouldn't take the risk of default to get folks in this town to work together and do their jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "should", "n't", "take", "the", "risk", "of", "default", "to", "get", "folks", "in", "this", "town", "to", "work", "together", "and", "do", "their", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Who else do you think can come out of this genuinely feeling it's been a good period for them?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "else", "do", "you", "think", "can", "come", "out", "of", "this", "genuinely", "feeling", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "good", "period", "for", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "In an odd way, the president of the United States wins even though he loses.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "an", "odd", "way", ",", "the", "president", "of", "the", "United", "States", "wins", "even", "though", "he", "loses", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "What's your assessment of where we are with this deal?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "assessment", "of", "where", "we", "are", "with", "this", "deal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "It's very simple, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "simple", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "WP", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What was it like for you to be with the congresswoman?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "it", "like", "for", "you", "to", "be", "with", "the", "congresswoman", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "Well, it's always wonderful to be with Gabby no matter -- no matter what opportunity you have to spend time with her.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "always", "wonderful", "to", "be", "with", "Gabby", "no", "matter", "--", "no", "matter", "what", "opportunity", "you", "have", "to", "spend", "time", "with", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "How would you describe her condition at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "her", "condition", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "ARUSONE: Well, I mean she's in this rehab program for a reason.", "answer_tokens": ["ARUSONE", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "mean", "she", "'s", "in", "this", "rehab", "program", "for", "a", "reason", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "What did she say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Well, on the way in and the way out, she just was emotional.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "on", "the", "way", "in", "and", "the", "way", "out", ",", "she", "just", "was", "emotional", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 199, "question": "So what -- what is her political aspiration now?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "--", "what", "is", "her", "political", "aspiration", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 200, "answer": "Well, you know, that's flattering of you to say, but, you know, for Gabby it's day by day right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "'s", "flattering", "of", "you", "to", "say", ",", "but", ",", "you", "know", ",", "for", "Gabby", "it", "'s", "day", "by", "day", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2009"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 220, "question": "Is this the Tea Party's finest hour?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "the", "Tea", "Party", "'s", "finest", "hour", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 221, "answer": "You know, I think the finest hour actually took place back in 2009 when the Tea Party started and the uprising began.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "the", "finest", "hour", "actually", "took", "place", "back", "in", "2009", "when", "the", "Tea", "Party", "started", "and", "the", "uprising", "began", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mark Meckler"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Who -- wouldn't be asking their politicians if this is the appropriate next step to take?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "--", "would", "n't", "be", "asking", "their", "politicians", "if", "this", "is", "the", "appropriate", "next", "step", "to", "take", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "But my problem, I guess, Mark Meckler, is that it's very easy to run into government on a ticker that we want to cut spending.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "my", "problem", ",", "I", "guess", ",", "Mark", "Meckler", ",", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "very", "easy", "to", "run", "into", "government", "on", "a", "ticker", "that", "we", "want", "to", "cut", "spending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Do you feel you're either of those things?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "you", "'re", "either", "of", "those", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I think it's crazy that the other side calls us so many names.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "crazy", "that", "the", "other", "side", "calls", "us", "so", "many", "names", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "So you have this division within your own party, don't you?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "have", "this", "division", "within", "your", "own", "party", ",", "do", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "To say it's within our own party is incorrect.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "say", "it", "'s", "within", "our", "own", "party", "is", "incorrect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "And could we see a scenario potentially following that argument where you would support Barack Obama in the next election?", "question_tokens": ["And", "could", "we", "see", "a", "scenario", "potentially", "following", "that", "argument", "where", "you", "would", "support", "Barack", "Obama", "in", "the", "next", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, that is a fact.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "is", "a", "fact", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "If you were John Boehner, how would you be feeling right now?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "were", "John", "Boehner", ",", "how", "would", "you", "be", "feeling", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "I'm sure John Boehner feels very frustrated and unappreciated.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "sure", "John", "Boehner", "feels", "very", "frustrated", "and", "unappreciated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John Boehner", "Dick Armey"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "NNS", "TO", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", ":", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Hilary Rosen, do you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Hilary", "Rosen", ",", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "The reason John Boehner didn't get more done was because unfortunately people like Dick Armey were out there sending out e-mails to groups of conservatives and -- and criticizing him, don't compromise with the president.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "reason", "John", "Boehner", "did", "n't", "get", "more", "done", "was", "because", "unfortunately", "people", "like", "Dick", "Armey", "were", "out", "there", "sending", "out", "e-mails", "to", "groups", "of", "conservatives", "and", "--", "and", "criticizing", "him", ",", "do", "n't", "compromise", "with", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hilary Rosen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "The Tea Party, by common consent, are the political winners in all of this, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["The", "Tea", "Party", ",", "by", "common", "consent", ",", "are", "the", "political", "winners", "in", "all", "of", "this", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Well, first of all, there's nobody that I know that's a Tea Party activist in America that sees themselves as part of a political party.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "there", "'s", "nobody", "that", "I", "know", "that", "'s", "a", "Tea", "Party", "activist", "in", "America", "that", "sees", "themselves", "as", "part", "of", "a", "political", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "You've got to say that at the moment, who takes on Obama?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "got", "to", "say", "that", "at", "the", "moment", ",", "who", "takes", "on", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "You know, and you've got the major Republican presidential candidates who, if they had their way, would have brought the country into default.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "and", "you", "'ve", "got", "the", "major", "Republican", "presidential", "candidates", "who", ",", "if", "they", "had", "their", "way", ",", "would", "have", "brought", "the", "country", "into", "default", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", ":", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Who stands right now?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "stands", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well, quite frankly, my own view is that President Obama has demonstrated himself to be -- first of all, he's so ideologically defined, he virtually understands nothing but income redistribution, and he's incompetent at even doing that, to the frustration of the --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "quite", "frankly", ",", "my", "own", "view", "is", "that", "President", "Obama", "has", "demonstrated", "himself", "to", "be", "--", "first", "of", "all", ",", "he", "'s", "so", "ideologically", "defined", ",", "he", "virtually", "understands", "nothing", "but", "income", "redistribution", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "incompetent", "at", "even", "doing", "that", ",", "to", "the", "frustration", "of", "the", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "However, what is the answer to my question, which is, which of all the candidates right now -- and there's a clear split ideologically between the Michele Bachmann end of things and the Mitt Romney end of things -- which of the candidates who have declared an interest so far do you believe could beat the president?", "question_tokens": ["However", ",", "what", "is", "the", "answer", "to", "my", "question", ",", "which", "is", ",", "which", "of", "all", "the", "candidates", "right", "now", "--", "and", "there", "'s", "a", "clear", "split", "ideologically", "between", "the", "Michele", "Bachmann", "end", "of", "things", "and", "the", "Mitt", "Romney", "end", "of", "things", "--", "which", "of", "the", "candidates", "who", "have", "declared", "an", "interest", "so", "far", "do", "you", "believe", "could", "beat", "the", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", ",", "WDT", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", ":", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ":", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "All of the above.", "answer_tokens": ["All", "of", "the", "above", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["billions of dollars"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "I mean, what would you say, Hilary?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "would", "you", "say", ",", "Hilary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "I think that no matter who they nominate, they're going to coalesce around the candidate and try and spend the billions of dollars to try and defeat the president.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "no", "matter", "who", "they", "nominate", ",", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "coalesce", "around", "the", "candidate", "and", "try", "and", "spend", "the", "billions", "of", "dollars", "to", "try", "and", "defeat", "the", "president", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hilary"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "When you heard about what had happened, as somebody that concocts these outrageous plot lines yourself, were you surprised by what you heard?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "heard", "about", "what", "had", "happened", ",", "as", "somebody", "that", "concocts", "these", "outrageous", "plot", "lines", "yourself", ",", "were", "you", "surprised", "by", "what", "you", "heard", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "I wasn't surprised by what I heard.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "n't", "surprised", "by", "what", "I", "heard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 421, "question": "Were you critical at all of the time it took the authorities there to get to that island?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "critical", "at", "all", "of", "the", "time", "it", "took", "the", "authorities", "there", "to", "get", "to", "that", "island", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 422, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Wouldn't you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "You would think so.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "would", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "What is the plot here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "plot", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "Well, my books -- I think one of the hallmarks of my thrillers is that they're based in reality.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "books", "--", "I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "hallmarks", "of", "my", "thrillers", "is", "that", "they", "'re", "based", "in", "reality", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steven King"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "What makes you, Brad Thor, an apparently normal guy, have these incredibly weird, random thoughts?", "question_tokens": ["What", "makes", "you", ",", "Brad", "Thor", ",", "an", "apparently", "normal", "guy", ",", "have", "these", "incredibly", "weird", ",", "random", "thoughts", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Steven King had a great line.", "answer_tokens": ["Steven", "King", "had", "a", "great", "line", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Brad Thor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Las Vegas"]}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Or happen?", "question_tokens": ["Or", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "Well, I always joke around that the Red Cell Program is the Las Vegas of government programs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "always", "joke", "around", "that", "the", "Red", "Cell", "Program", "is", "the", "Las", "Vegas", "of", "government", "programs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What was the fallout like for you personally after that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "fallout", "like", "for", "you", "personally", "after", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "We got a lot of threats, which was not easy for me as a husband and father.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "got", "a", "lot", "of", "threats", ",", "which", "was", "not", "easy", "for", "me", "as", "a", "husband", "and", "father", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "What was that like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "that", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "That for me was as great as it was -- being part of the Red Cell Program, that for me was a dream come true.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "for", "me", "was", "as", "great", "as", "it", "was", "--", "being", "part", "of", "the", "Red", "Cell", "Program", ",", "that", "for", "me", "was", "a", "dream", "come", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110802pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Do you think it's a more dangerous world now than it was in 2001?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "more", "dangerous", "world", "now", "than", "it", "was", "in", "2001", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2001"]}}]